Analysts factors are derived from the published reports
分析师因子来自投资银行的
of sell-side research analysts at investment banks.
卖方分析师发布的报告
Their reports include ratings such as buy, hold, or sell.
这些报告包括评级 例如买入 持有或卖出
They also include earnings estimates or price targets for the stock.
还包括股票的收益估值或价格目标
Sell-side analysts may be assigned to a few companies within the same industry,
卖方分析师可能会分配给同一行业的几家公司
and may even meet with the management of the companies that they evaluate.
甚至可能会与要评估的企业高管见面
This research is intended for
这种研究面向买方投资公司
buy-side investment firms such as mutual funds and hedge funds,
例如共同基金和对冲基金
who execute their trades with these sell-side investment banks.
他们与卖方投资银行进行交易
Since many large investment firms value the opinions or research analysts,
因为很多大型投资公司很重视分析师的意见
their published analysis can have significant effects on stock trading.
所以分析师发布的报告可能对股票交易有很大的影响
If you read financial news and the news mentioned that
如果你阅读财经新闻
a particular stock has a buy or hold rating,
新闻提到某个股票具有买入或持有评级
this is likely an average rating of multiple research analysts.
那么这有可能是多个分析师的平均评级
We may also refer to analyst ratings as a kind of sentiment factor
我们还会将分析师评级称为情感因子
because each research analysts
因为每个分析师
aggregates their information about the company's financials,
都会将公司的财务报告
it's growth prospects as well as its current price,
增长前景和当前股价结合到一起
and then summarizes this into the analysts overall
然后总结为总体结果
conclusion or sentiment about that stock.
或对该股票的情感
Investment banks choose their own rating scale.
投资银行有自己的评级量表
For example, one has buy, neutral, or sell.
例如 买入 中立或卖出
Another has overweight, equal weight,
或者权重过高 权重相等
underweight, or more volatile.
权重过低或更波动
Yet another has trading by, recommended list,
还有的是交易 推荐列表
market out performer, market performer and market underperformer.
市场表现很佳者 市场参与者和市场表现不佳者
Sell-side ratings are usually aggregated to
卖方评级通常汇总为
create a consensus sentiment about a particular stock.
关于特定股票的一致情感
It's also useful to focus on when analysts change their ratings.
专门观察分析师何时更改评级也很有用
For example, if multiple analysts start
例如 如果多位分析师
changing their ratings of a stock from hold to sell,
开始将股票的评级从持有变成卖出
we might expect investors who follow analyst ratings to start selling that stock.
那么预计遵循分析师评级的投资者可能会开始卖出该股票
Analyst ratings may experience a heard mentality.
分析师评级可能会出现从众心理
It's difficult for a single analyst to publish a sell rating
当业内大部分其他分析师都发布买入评级时
when most other analysts in the industry are publishing a buy rating.
单个分析师一般不会发布卖出评级
In other words, it's safer to be wrong when everyone else is also wrong,
也就是说 当所有其他人都错误时 某个分析师错误了成本更低
but more costly for an analyst to be wrong when everyone else is right.
但是当所有其他人都正确时 某个分析师错误了成本更高
So instead of taking a simple average of analyst ratings,
所以与其直接计算分析师评级的平均结果
it may be useful to focus on
有必要侧重于
the most reputable star analysts and give their ratings more weight.
最有声望的星级分析师并使他们的评价权重更高
One way to combine analyst sentiment into a trading signal is to aggregate
将分析师情感添加到交易信号中的一种方式是
all the ratings that have changed over a certain period such as the past three months.
将过去一段时间（例如过去三个月）有变化的所有评级汇总起来
If we count all the ratings upgrades and subtract all the ratings downgrades,
如果将所有评级升级考虑在内并减去所有评级降级
then we have a number that is either positive, negative or 0.
那么会获得一个为正 为负或为 0 的数字
A positive number represents a positive sentiment,
正数表示正面情感
whereas a negative number is a negative sentiment.
负数表示负面情感
To rescale this sentiment between negative 1 and 1,
要将情感值调整到 -1 到 1 之间
we could divide this number by the total number of analysts that we're tracking,
可以将此数字除以跟踪的分析师总数
whether they upgraded, downgraded or cut their rating the same.
无论是升级了 降级了还是保持不变